carlos bobadilla jr

Email: bobadilla.jr@gmail.com Phone: bobadilla.info

SUMMARY

I'm a UX Developer. I deigned UI for 10+ years, but love developing.

My process goes from sketches, whiteboards to user flows, and I use Sketch. I'm a fan of HTML/CSS. I enjoy working in Illustrator and Photoshop. git is the greatest. I like reading Designer News. I love the Lakers and catching the latest in mobile, at Pttrns.

OBJECTIVES

I'm currently a UX developer at AppOne. I've previously worked with Handmade

Mobile, 2Bit Circus, and Netflix

In my free time I work on GravitiWorks, a magnet tech solution company I co-founded.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Art Institute santa Monica, CA (Graduated January 2001)

Computer Animation/ Design

EXPERIENCE

Appone Santa Monica, CA (August 2014– Present)

UX Developer

On a daily basis I am working on user flow for all company related IOS/Android, and working on new designs for upcoming releases.

Handmade Mobile Santa Monica, CA (January 2014– July 2014)

Sr UX/UI Mobile Developer

- Develop Mobile Apps for native IOS
- UX user flows and structure
- Objective C, HTML5

Two Bit Circus Los Angeles, CA (December 2012 – January 2014)

Sr. UX/UI Designer

- Directed and delegated to project creative team and outside vendors
- Created comps, storyboards, initial graphic concepts and final deliverables
- Built and maintained relationships with clients, partner agencies and other vendors.

Netflix Beverly Hills, CA (April 2012– December 2012)

Sr. UI Art Director

- Maintained UI brand across multiple platforms
- Developed and presented conceptual solutions for web, iPhone, Xbox, and Playstation
- Assisted production managers in maintaining consistent user experience

SKILLS

